[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie I Am Sam, when is Sam and Lucys IHOP night?", "correct_answer": "every Wednesday", "incorrect_answers": ["every Tuesday", "every Saturday", "every Friday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This artiodactyl mammal is the closest surviving relative of the giraffe.", "correct_answer": "Okapi", "incorrect_answers": ["Tapir", "Llama", "Zebra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From 1888-1889, American traders Simon and Thomas Metcalfe brought some men from Manila to the Western Hemisphere. Which state did they bring them to?", "correct_answer": "Alaska", "incorrect_answers": ["California", "Mexico", "Oregon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest city on the worlds largest island?", "correct_answer": "Godthaab", "incorrect_answers": ["Rabaul", "Frobisher Bay", "Weser"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This German car brand, founded in 1919, is nicknamed Beamer in English.", "correct_answer": "BMW", "incorrect_answers": ["Volkswagen", "Opel", "Audi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aristotle believed in the existence of this anatomical difference between human males and females.", "correct_answer": "Males had more teeth.", "incorrect_answers": ["Females were born without a brain, and it was formed later.", "All of these", "Males had more kidneys."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Han Solos first mate on the Millennium Falcon?", "correct_answer": "Chewbacca", "incorrect_answers": ["R2-D2", "Darth Vader", "Yoda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Michelangelos statue of David is housed in what city?", "correct_answer": "Florence", "incorrect_answers": ["Turin", "Rome", "Vienna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Consider all animals that ever lived. Which animal had the longest teeth?", "correct_answer": "The straight-tusked elephant", "incorrect_answers": ["The Malaysian elephant.", "The mammoth", "The Asian elephant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On one of the Durham Bulls bus rides, Crash describes life in the Show. How long did Crash say he was in the Show?", "correct_answer": "21 days", "incorrect_answers": ["10 days", "A week", "30 days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venomous and poisonous are two different terms. What does the term venomous refer to?", "correct_answer": "Animals that inject venom", "incorrect_answers": ["Animals that are deadly when eaten", "Plants and animals that secrete venom and are harmful when touched", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film is a 2005 remake of the 1980 John Carpenter film of the same name.", "correct_answer": "The Fog", "incorrect_answers": ["The Thing", "The Hills Have Eyes", "The Hitcher"]}]